This is similar.
Basically, you're going to take the fabric and keep rolling around basically up your ankle, your calf and your leg.
Do this very slowly.
Make sure that you're basically the folds are very strong and over.
Otherwise, it will come undone.
You don't want that.
So, definitely keep going up the leg all the way to the top here.
Now, you'll notice actually that the underline fabric in this case is white.
That's okay.
It doesn't really matter if it's green or white.
Actually, indeed with the stocking colors you're going to see, it's going to flow very nicely from the green to one of the few areas of our costume that won't be green.
Now, you want to keep going up your leg right about to the mid-calf level.
That's as far up you want to go.